A Guide to the Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music records FA1420
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1955-1983; 1; 58.87 Cubic Feet 155 letter-size document boxes. Boxes 1-155.
  - R-S-T-U-V
    - Van Wych, Wilfrid (Box 145, Folder 24)
    - Varga, Ruben (Box 145, Folder 25)
    - Vartenissian, Shakeh (Box 145, Folder 26)
    - Vasary, Tamas (Box 145, Folder 27)
    - Vassar College (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Vassiliades, Evangeline (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Vaughn, Denis (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Vaughn Williams Memorial Library (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Vazquez, Lupo (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Vazsonyi, Balint (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Veal, Charles (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Velasco, Luisa (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Vellutino, Renato (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Venezia, Guiuseppe (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Veneziano, Rita (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Ventriglia, Franco (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Venora, Lee (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Verdejo, Awilda (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Vered, Ilana (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Veri and Jamanis (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Vermont Council on the Humanities and Public Issues (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Vermont Symphony Orchestra Association (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - Vernon, William (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - Veronica, Anne (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - Verrett, Shirley (Box 146, Folder 21)
    - Versalle, Richard (Box 146, Folder 22)
    - Vertress, Julie (Box 146, Folder 23)
    - Viglione, Gina (Box 146, Folder 24)
    - Vincent, Ellen (Box 146, Folder 25)
    - Virginia Opera Association - Brochures (Box 146, Folder 26)
    - Virizlay, Mihaly (Box 146, Folder 27)
    - Virkhaus, Nancy (Box 146, Folder 28)
    - Virostek, Linda (Box 146, Folder 29)
    - Vitale, Michael (Box 146, Folder 30)
    - Vitto, E. (Box 146, Folder 31)
    - Viviano, Samuel (Box 146, Folder 32)
    - Vokes, Emmett (Box 146, Folder 33)
    - Voketaitis, Arnold (Box 146, Folder 34)
    - Volek, Joan (Box 146, Folder 35)
    - Von Sauer, Mme. Angelica Morales (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Von Wurtzler, Mr. Aristid (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Vose, Madelyn (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - W-X-Y-Z
    - Wadsworth, Atheneum, Hartford, CT (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Wafford, Catherine Owens (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Wagner, Janet (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Wagner Renaissance Opera Company (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Wahman, William (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Waid, Guy (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Wainner, James (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Waisaman, Leonardo (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Waite, William (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Waitzman, Daniel (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Waldorf, Stanley (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Walker, Annie Torita (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Walker, Clyde (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Walker, Donald (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Walker, Frances (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - Walker, John (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - Walker, Mallory (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - Wall, Joan (Box 147, Folder 21)
    - Wallace, Catherine (Box 147, Folder 22)
    - Wallace, Mervin (Box 147, Folder 23)
    - Wallace, Robert (Box 147, Folder 24)
    - Wallace, William (Box 147, Folder 25)
    - Waller, Juanita (Box 147, Folder 26)
    - Walser, Lloyd A. (Box 147, Folder 27)
    - Walters, Barbara Ann (Box 147, Folder 28)
    - Walters, Carole (Box 147, Folder 29)
    - Walters, Gwendolyn (Box 147, Folder 30)
    - Walters, Jeannette (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Wandzura, Mr. Tadej (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Warburton, Thomas Jr. (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Ware, Clifton (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Warkow, Stewart (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Warner, Beverly (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Warner, Edward (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Warner, Martha Stotler (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Warren, Bette (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Warren, Coletta (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Warren, Forest (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Warren, Roger (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Washington, Barbara (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Washington County Museum of Fine Arts (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Washington Square Association (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Washington University (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - Wates, Miss Roye (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Watkins, Gordon (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Watson, Laurence (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - Watson, Sandra (Box 148, Folder 20)
    - Watts, Edward (Box 148, Folder 21)
    - Weathers, Felicia (Box 148, Folder 22)
    - Webber, Constance (Box 148, Folder 23)
    - Webber, Lynne (Box 148, Folder 24)
    - Weber, Barton (Box 148, Folder 25)
    - Weekley and Arganbright (Box 148, Folder 26)
    - Weeks, Dallas (Box 148, Folder 27)
    - Weide, Genevieve (Box 148, Folder 28)
    - Weidensaul, Jane (Box 148, Folder 29)
    - Weiler, William (Box 148, Folder 30)
    - Weimer, Eric (Box 148, Folder 31)
    - Weinstein, Burton (Box 148, Folder 32)
    - Weiss, Carole (Box 148, Folder 33)
    - Weiss, Irene (Box 148, Folder 34)
    - Weiss, Naomi (Box 148, Folder 35)
    - Welch, Samuel C. (Box 148, Folder 36)
    - Weldon, Elaine (Box 148, Folder 37)
    - Weldon, Irene (Box 148, Folder 38)
    - Wellesley College - Summer Workshop in Forepiano (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Wells, David (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Wells, Eleanor (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Wells, Nikita (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Welch, Besse (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Welting, Ruth (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Weltman, Marianne (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Wendell, Cecilia (Sheryl Crane) (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Wentling, Roberta Ann (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Wentworth, Kenneth and Jean (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Wesley, Elaine (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Wesleyan University (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - Wesp, Beverly (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - West, Gene (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - West, James H. (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - West, John (Box 149, Folder 16)
    - West, Lucretia (Box 149, Folder 17)
    - Westerman, Dale (Box 149, Folder 18)
    - West Coast Auditions, 1978-1979 (Box 149, Folder 19)
    - West Coast Auditions, 1977 (Box 149, Folder 20)
    - West Coast Auditions, 1976 (Box 149, Folder 21)
    - West Coast Auditions, 1975 (Box 149, Folder 22)
    - West Coast Auditions, 1974 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - West Coast Auditions, 1973 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Western Opera Theatre - Correspondence and Programs, 1967-1970 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Westminster Records (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Westminster Choir College (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Weston, Geoffrey C. (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Westport School of Music, Inc. (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - West Virginia Opera Company (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - WETA-TV (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Wheeler, Margaret (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Wheless, William (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Whisler, Bruce (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - White, Claudia (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - White, Dorothy (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - White, Edward (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - White, Lawrence (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - White, Lois (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - White, Robert (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - White, Sylvia Stone (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - White, Willard (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Whitefield, Bernard (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Whiteman, Lois (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Whitney, Gloria (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - John Hay Whitney Foundation (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Whitney, Ryan (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Whittier College, Whittier, CA (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Widoff, Justine (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Wieck, Grace (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Wieder, Grace (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Wiench, Nancy (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Wilcox, Albert (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Wilcox, Glenn (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Wilder, David (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - Wildes, Rose (Box 151, Folder 18)
    - Wiles, John A. (Box 151, Folder 19)
    - Wilkes, Jocelyn (Box 151, Folder 20)
    - Williams, Charles E. (Box 151, Folder 21)
    - Williams College (Box 151, Folder 22)
    - Williams, David (Box 151, Folder 23)
    - Williams, Edna (Box 151, Folder 24)
    - Williams, Gwendolyn (Box 151, Folder 25)
    - Williams, John Joseph (Box 151, Folder 26)
    - Williams, Katherine (Box 151, Folder 27)
    - Williams, Laverne (Box 151, Folder 28)
    - Williams, Linda Kay (Box 151, Folder 29)
    - Williams, Millard (Box 151, Folder 30)
    - Williams, Norma (Box 151, Folder 31)
    - Williams, Nyal Zeno (Box 151, Folder 32)
    - Williams, Phyllis Wilcox (Box 151, Folder 33)
    - Williams, R. Paul (Box 151, Folder 34)
    - Williams, Ralph (Box 151, Folder 35)
    - Williams, Robert J. (Box 151, Folder 36)
    - Williamson, Robert (Box 151, Folder 37)
    - Williford, Martha (Box 151, Folder 38)
    - Willis, Laraine (Box 151, Folder 39)
    - Willis, Richard (Box 151, Folder 40)
    - Willy, Jeannette (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Wilmington Opera Society (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Wilmington Society of Fine Arts (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Wilsen, Carlotta (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, James (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, James Mitchell (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, Karen (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Robert (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, Roy (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, Thomas E. (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Winchester, John A. (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Winden, Joan and William (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Winerock, Jack (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Wing, Stafford (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Wininger, Judith (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Winkler, Margreet (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Winklhoffer, Sharon (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - Winn, Dorothy (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - Winston. Lee (Box 152, Folder 19)
    - Winston, Patricia (Box 152, Folder 20)
    - Winter, Robert (Box 152, Folder 21)
    - Winthrop, Frederick (Box 152, Folder 22)
    - Wion, John (Box 152, Folder 23)
    - Wise, Herschel (Box 152, Folder 24)
    - Wise, Patricia (Box 152, Folder 25)
    - Wisehardt, Frederika (Box 152, Folder 26)
    - Wiseman, John (Box 152, Folder 27)
    - Witt, Susan (Box 152, Folder 28)
    - Wittman, Joan Aceto (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Witowska, Nadja (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - WHCN (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Wnek, Judith (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - WNET - Performance Programs (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - WNYC (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Wodehouse, Ms. Artis (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Wold, Susan (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - Wolf, Peter (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Wolf, R. Peter (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Wolfe, Paul (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Wolfe, Walter (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Wolff, Inge (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Wolff, William (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - Wong, Grace (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - Woodruff, William (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - Woods, Forbes (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - Worth, Mara (Box 153, Folder 19)
    - Worthington, Phyllis Richmond (Box 153, Folder 20)
    - Woodul, Charles (Box 153, Folder 21)
    - Worchester Art Museum (Box 153, Folder 22)
    - Workman, William (Box 153, Folder 23)
    - Wright, Carole (Box 153, Folder 24)
    - Wright, Elayne (Box 153, Folder 25)
    - Wright, Elizabeth (Box 153, Folder 26)
    - Wright, Ms. Leslie A. (Box 153, Folder 27)
    - WRVR (Box 153, Folder 28)
    - Wu, Francis Chi-Tza (Box 153, Folder 29)
    - Wuorinen, Charles (Box 153, Folder 30)
    - Wyatt, Dorcas (Box 153, Folder 31)
    - Wyatt, Keith (Box 153, Folder 32)
    - Wyatt, W. E. (Box 153, Folder 33)
    - Wycoff, Lou Ann (Box 153, Folder 34)
    - Wymond, Jane (Box 153, Folder 35)
    - Wyner, Nancy (Box 153, Folder 36)
    - Wyner, Susan Davenny (Box 153, Folder 37)
    - Wyrzykowska, Maria (Box 153, Folder 38)
    - Wysocki, Marie (Box 153, Folder 39)
    - Yaddo (Box 153, Folder 40)
    - Yaffe, John-Burton (Box 153, Folder 41)
    - Yajima, Mr. Mas (Box 153, Folder 42)
    - Yakutis, Mr. R. Kazys (Box 153, Folder 43)
    - Yale - Journal of Music Theory (Box 153, Folder 44)
    - Yampolsky, Miron (Box 153, Folder 45)
    - Yancy, Alexander (Box 153, Folder 46)
    - Yankauskas, Elizabeth (Box 153, Folder 47)
    - Yankelev, Yosef (Box 153, Folder 48)
    - Yarbrough and Cowan (Box 153, Folder 49)
    - Yarbrough, Joan (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Yarick, Doris (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Yarick, George (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Yarnell, Bruce (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Yaron, Jacob (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Yates, Gary (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Yauger, Margaret (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Yeadon, Pearl (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Yerushalmi, Ophra (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Yockey, Joann (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Yoes, Janice (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Young Artists Plan (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Young Artists as Soloists with Symphony Orchestra (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Young Audiences, Inc. (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - Young Concert Artists - Correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - Young, Gary (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Young, John (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Young, Landon (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Young, Lauretta (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Young, Stephen Edward (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Younger, Charles (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Youth Symphony Orchestra of New York (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Yule, Don (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Zamaro, Dino (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Zambrana, Margarita (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Zango, Lillian (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Zara, Meredith (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Zayas, Juana (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Zeiset, Dorothy (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Zeitlin, Zvi (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Zeleny, Sister Margaret (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Zermatt Project (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Zerul, Eileen (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - Zilboorg, Olga (Box 155, Folder 19)
    - Zimansky, Robert (Box 155, Folder 20)
    - Zimmerman, Edward (Box 155, Folder 21)
    - Ziskin, Loretta (Box 155, Folder 22)
    - Zolas, Edward (Box 155, Folder 23)
    - Zschau, Marilyn (Box 155, Folder 24)
    - Zubin, Kathryn (Box 155, Folder 25)
    - Zukofsky, Paul (Box 155, Folder 26)
    - Zumbro, Nicholas (Box 155, Folder 27)
    - Zuponcic, Miss Veda (Box 155, Folder 28)
    - Zutavern, Georgia Ann (Box 155, Folder 29)
    - Zvi, Idith (Box 155, Folder 30)
- Project Files, 1957-1983; 2; 46.33 Cubic Feet 122 letter document boxes. Boxes 156-277.
  - A-B-C-D
    - Adler, Samuel (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Adolphe, Bruce (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Advancement for Early Music and Dance in New York - New York Cornet and Sacbut Ensemble (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Affiliate Artists-Fund for Music Joint Venture (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Affiliate Artists, Inc. - Dockets (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Agee, Richard (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Ahlstrom, David C. (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Albert, Stephen (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Albuquerque Opera Theatre (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Aler, John (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Algie, Stephen (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Allen, Judith Shatin (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Allen, Susan (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - All-Media Dramatic Workshop (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Alternative Center for International Arts, inc. (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - American Artists Abroad - Amarta (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - The American Brass Chamber Music Association, Inc. (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - American Composers Concerts, Inc. (American Composers Orchestra) (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - American Dance Festival (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - American Guild of Organists (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - American Institute of Verdi Studies (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - American Music Center - Correspondence, 1970-1980 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - American Society of Composers and Publishers (ASCAP) (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - American Society of University Composers (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League (ASOL) - Financial material (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - American Women Composers (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Amlin, Martin (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Anders, Lynda (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Anderson, Adelaida A. (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Anderson, Beth (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Anderson, Carl (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Anderson, June (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Anderson, Sally (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - An Die Musik Quintet (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - And-Or Service (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - And-Or Service (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Andrews, Joyce Ann (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Andrews, Marsha (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Andrus, Donald (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report (Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music), 1970-1981 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Appel, Toby (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Applebaum, Edward (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Apple Hill Chamber Players (Center for Chamber Music at Apple Hill Farm, Inc.) (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Appleton, Jon (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Archetto, Maria Anne (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Arden, David (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Ariel Chamber Ensemble (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Arioso Trio (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Arizona Opera Company (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Arkansas Opera Theatre, Inc. (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Arneson, Sally (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Arnold, Elizabeth (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Arnold, Johana (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Arnold, Michael (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Arnold, Donna (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Arriola, Pablo (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - ARS Musica, Ann Arbor, MI (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Art and Urban Resources, Inc. (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Artists International (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Ashley, Kathleen (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Ashley, Robert (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Asia, Daniel (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Asman, Kathryn (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Aston Magna Foundation for Music, Inc. (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Atamian, Dickran (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Atherton, Peter (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Atlanta Chamber Players (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Atlanta Civic Opera Association, Inc. (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Aubrey, Elizabeth (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Audubon Quartet (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Aulos Ensemble (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Austin, Robert (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Babcock, Bruce (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - Bachlund, Gary (Box 162, Folder 14)
    - Bachmann, Rhonda (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - Bachmann, Sarah (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - Bailey, Walter B. (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - Baker, Larry (Box 162, Folder 18)
    - Baker, Thomas (Box 162, Folder 19)
    - Baker, Timothy (Box 162, Folder 20)
    - Baker, W. Claude (Box 162, Folder 21)
    - Baksa, Robert (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Balk, Leo (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Ball, Alan (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Ballou, Stephen (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Baltimore Symphony - Young Artists (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Bachetto Musicale (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Banducci, Antonia (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Bardera, Andre (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Barclay, Diane (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Barnes, Edward (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Barnes, Sheila (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Barnett, Connie (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Baron, Carol K. (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Barr, Pamela (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Baskin, Theodore (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Bassett, Ralph (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Bates, Leon (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Baton Rouge Opera (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Battersby, Edmund (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Battle, Kathleen (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Battles, Clyde (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Baur, John (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Baxter, Carol (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Baygulova, Mara (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Beall, John (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Beasley, Cecily (Box 164, Folder 14)
    - Beatty, Sarah (Box 164, Folder 15)
    - Becker, Richard (Box 164, Folder 16)
    - Becker, Robert (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - Beckstrom, Lynn (Box 164, Folder 18)
    - Bedford, Cynthia (Box 164, Folder 19)
    - Beerman, Burton (Box 164, Folder 20)
    - Behr, Randall (Box 164, Folder 21)
    - Behr, Wayne (Box 164, Folder 22)
    - Behrens, Jack (Box 164, Folder 23)
    - Behrman, David (Box 164, Folder 24)
    - Bel Canto Opera (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Belen, Martha (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Bell, Kenneth (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Bell, Larry (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Belling, Susan (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Bender, Cortlandt (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Bender, Howard (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Benjamin, Thomas (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Benner, Joan (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Bennett, Frank (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Bennett, Lawrence (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - Bennett, Stephen (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Benser, Caroline Coker Cepin (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Benshoof, Kenneth (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Benson, Jacquelyn (Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Benson and Hedges Music Festival (Box 165, Folder 16)
    - Berg, Christopher (Box 165, Folder 17)
    - Berg, Rebecca (Box 165, Folder 18)
    - Berg, Sigrid (Box 165, Folder 19)
    - Bergell, Aaron (Box 165, Folder 20)
    - Berger, Mr. Karol (Box 165, Folder 21)
    - Bergquist, Eleanor (Box 165, Folder 22)
    - Bergsma, William (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Berinbaum, Martin (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Berkofsky, Martin (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Berland, Cynthia (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Berliner, Paul (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Berne, Pamela (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Bernat, Mark (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Bernsienne, Ernest-Henri (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Bernsten, Andrea (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Beskyd, Tetjana (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Best, Julius (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Best, Stuart (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - Betjeman, Paul (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - Bevelander, Brian (Box 166, Folder 14)
    - Bieler, Ida (Box 166, Folder 15)
    - Biggs, John (Box 166, Folder 16)
    - Billeter, Mary (Box 166, Folder 17)
    - Bills, John (Box 166, Folder 18)
    - Birnbaum, Charles (Box 166, Folder 19)
    - Birnbaum, Leila (Box 166, Folder 20)
    - Biscardi, Chester (Box 166, Folder 21)
    - Bishop, Raymond (Box 166, Folder 22)
    - Bitkoff, Bruce (Box 166, Folder 23)
    - Bitting, Richard (Box 166, Folder 24)
    - Bjarnason, Kristi (Ms.) (Box 166, Folder 25)
    - Blachly, H. Alexander (Box 166, Folder 26)
    - Black, Lenora (Box 166, Folder 27)
    - Black, Robert (saxophone) (Box 166, Folder 28)
    - Black, Robert (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Black, William (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Blackearth Percussion Group (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Blackshere, Lawrence (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Blackstone, Marcia (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Blaney, Michael (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Blank, Allan (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Blasi, Angela Maria (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Blaustein, Susan (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Blauvelt, Ralph (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Blazer, Judith (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - Block, Steven (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - Bloom, Arthur (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Bloom, Claudia (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - Bloom, Peter (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - Bloom, Sarah Lambert (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - Blount, Gilbert (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - Blount, William (Box 167, Folder 18)
    - Blowers, Renee (Box 167, Folder 19)
    - Blum, Carole (Box 167, Folder 20)
    - Blum, Suzanne (Box 167, Folder 21)
    - Blumenthal, Daniel (Box 167, Folder 22)
    - Blumenfeld, Harold (Box 167, Folder 23)
    - Boal, Ellen TeSelle (Box 167, Folder 24)
    - Boardman, Christine (Box 167, Folder 25)
    - Boatrite, Harold (Box 167, Folder 26)
    - Boatwright, Cheryl (Box 167, Folder 27)
    - Bodnar-Horton, Nina (Box 167, Folder 28)
    - Bodzin, Zelma (Box 167, Folder 29)
    - Boehm Quintette, Inc. (Box 167, Folder 30)
    - Boelter, Karl (Box 167, Folder 31)
    - Bolden, Diane (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Bolle, James (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Bomstein, Catherine (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Bond, Rowland (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Bond, Victoria (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Boney, Allen (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Bonge, Dale (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Bookhout, Sharon Markovich (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Books, Donald (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Bookspan, Janet (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Boomer, Virgina (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - Boone, Charles (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - Booth, Thomas (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - Borders, James (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Boriskin, Michael (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Bornstein, Charles (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - Borschel, Audrey (Box 168, Folder 17)
    - Bossert, James Robert (Box 168, Folder 18)
    - The Boston Camerata, Inc. (Box 168, Folder 19)